Finding Aid for JJR Inc. photographic slides, 1960s-1990s
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
JJR Inc. photographic slides 1960s-1990s
JJR Inc.
35 linear feet
2011155 Bb 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection came from the organization (donor no. 5262 ) in September 2011.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
JJR was founded in Ann Arbor, Michigan in 1961 by the landscape architects William Johnson, Carl Johnson and Clarence Roy. Johnson, Johnson and Roy's first commission was a campus master plan for the University of Michigan. This project introduced the firm's innovative "framework" approach, which went on to become a widely accepted benchmark for land use and development planning.
In the early 1970s, Johnson John & Roy merged with Smith, Hinchman & Grylls (SHG) establishing the firm which in 1999 became SmithGroup. In 1975, William Johnson retired to assume the post of Dean, School of Natural Resources at the University of Michigan. In the decades that followed, JJR continued to operate under its original name as a sister company to SmithGroup, establishing additional offices and adding civil engineers, planners, urban designers and environmental specialists emphasizing an interdisciplinary approach. Known for projects in campus planning, environmental analysis, community development, and historic preservation, its many recognized projects include the University of Wisconsin Master Plan and subsequent development (1963-), Ann Arbor, Michigan; Lighthouse Landing (1978), Evanston, Illinois; and Franconia Notch (1989), White Mountain, New Hampshire. Carl Johnson retired in 1989, followed by Clarence Roy in 1992. The firm continues as part of SmithGroup, and took the name JJR Incorporated in 1997.
The JJR photographic slide collection relates solely to the firm's Michigan projects. The files are arranged into three series: Michigan; University of Michigan; and Other Michigan Universities. Included are slides of project sites (with some aerial images), site plans, and conceptual drawings. Although the collection covers the entire state, the bulk of the slides relate to southeast and lower Michigan, especially Ann Arbor, Detroit, Flint, Grand Rapids, and Saginaw. The files are in the order maintained by the organization. There is thus some overlap between the general Michigan series and the University of Michigan and Other Michigan Universities series. The researcher is advised to examine the finding aid closely.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Architectural firms--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Business districts--Michigan.; Campus planning--Michigan.; City planning--Michigan.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.); Flint (Mich.); Grand Rapids (Mich.); Saginaw (Mich.); University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan--Campus.; University of Michigan--Planning.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Slides (photography)
- Michigan Project files
  - AATA (Ann Arbor Transportation Authority) (Box 1)
  - Abbott Parkside E. Lansing (Box 1)
  - ACO (Box 1)
  - Adrian Central Business District (Box 1)
  - African American Museum (Box 1)
  - Albion / Albion College, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - America Aggregates (Box 1)
  - American Commerce Center (Box 1)
  - Angell Hall Façade (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Apartments (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Central Business District (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Farmer's Market (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Greenways (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Highway Study (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Housing Study (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Jackson Road (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Library Block (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Promenade (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Scenes (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Sculpture Park (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Old Main Parking (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Old West Side (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor S. Main St. 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Superior Township District Study (Box 2)
  - Ann Arbor Tech Park (Box 2)
  - Arbor Hills (Box 2)
  - Arborland (Box 2)
  - Arcadia Township (Box 2)
  - Art Van Furniture, Ann Arbor (Box 2)
  - Auburn Hills, The Palace (Box 2)
  - B&K, Canton (Box 2)
  - Baker/Zeeb Rd. (Box 2)
  - Bald Mountain II (Box 2)
  - Bald Mountain Recreational Area Repairs (Box 2)
  - Barton Hills (Box 2)
  - BASF-Biotech (Box 2)
  - BASF-Pt. Hennepin (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Airport (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Central Area Plan (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Festival Park (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Friendship Park (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Health Systems (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Mall / BC Mall Presentation, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Sojourner Truth Monument (Box 2)
  - Battle Creek Parks (Box 3)
  - Battle Creek Promontory (Box 3)
  - Battle Creek Super Block (Box 3)
  - Battle Creek Transamerica (Box 3)
  - Bay City Beachfront (Box 3)
  - Bay County Waterfront (Box 3)
  - Bay Field Commons (Box 3)
  - Bay Harbor (Box 3)
  - Beaumont Hospital, Royal Oak (Box 3)
  - Bechtel Corp. (Box 3)
  - Belle Isle Canal Rehab (Box 3)
  - Belle Isle Detroit Golf Course (Box 3)
  - Bing Steel (Box 3)
  - Bingham Farms (Box 3)
  - Bingham Farms Office Center (Box 3)
  - Birmingham Maplewood Pres (Box 3)
  - Birmingham Urban Design (Box 3)
  - Birmingham Henrietta St. Pilot (Box 3)
  - Birmingham Civic Center (Box 3)
  - Birmingham Townhouses (Box 3)
  - Birmingham Urban Design Sidewalks/Pathways, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - Black River Property (Box 4)
  - Boardman River (Box 4)
  - Bon Secours Convalescent Hospital (Box 4)
  - Boyne City, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Boyne City Housing / Zoning, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Boyne City Lakefront / Storefront Rehab, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Boyne Highlands (Box 4)
  - Boyne Mountain (Box 4)
  - Briarwood, Novi (Box 4)
  - Broadway Bridges, Ann Arbor (Box 4)
  - BRW/McLouth Waterfront (Box 4)
  - Cadillac-Fairview (Box 4)
  - Camp Holly (Box 4)
  - Capital City Airport (Box 4)
  - Capital Loop (Box 4)
  - Catherine McCauley Health (Box 4)
  - Charlevoix County Planning (Box 4)
  - Chelsea Downtown (Box 4)
  - Chrysler/Dodge, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Chrysler Highland Park Reuse Study (Box 5)
  - Chrysler Introl (Box 5)
  - Ciesin (Box 5)
  - Clark Street Tech Park (Box 5)
  - Comerica (Box 5)
  - Comerica Operation (Box 5)
  - Comshare (Box 5)
  - Conner's Marsh -- Au Sable River (Box 5)
  - Concordia College (Box 5)
  - Consumers Power-East Lansing Substation (Box 5)
  - Consumers Power-Powerline Study (Box 5)
  - Consumers Power-Ludington Pumped Storage (Box 5)
  - Consumers Power-Midland (Box 5)
  - Cornerstone (Box 5)
  - Cranbrook Marketing (Box 5)
  - Cranbrook School (Box 5)
  - Crossroads Village (Box 5)
  - Crosswinds (Box 6)
  - Dearborn Center (Box 6)
  - Dearborn Country Clubs (Box 6)
  - Dearborn Hills (Box 6)
  - Dearborn/Mayors Task Force (Box 6)
  - Detroit (Box 6)
  - Detroit Campus Martius (Box 6)
  - Detroit CBD Peoplemover (Box 6)
  - Detroit Civic Plaza/Cultural Center (Box 6)
  - Detroit-Comerica Park, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Detroit Community Reinvestment Strategy '97 (Box 6)
  - Detroit Edison Greenwood Community Reinvestment Strategy (Box 6)
  - Detroit Grand River / Greenfield (Box 6)
  - Detroit Greening (Box 6)
  - Detroit-Hart Plaza (Box 6)
  - DIA (Box 7)
  - DIA / DOC (Box 7)
  - Detroit Institute of Technology (Box 7)
  - Greater Detroit, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Detroit -- Grand River/Greenfield (Box 7)
  - Detroit Medical Center (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro Activity Center (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro General (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro Graphics (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro Northwest Air (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro Wetlands (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro-Wayne County Air Show 1992 (Box 7)
  - Detroit Metro World Centre (Box 7)
  - Detroit Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Detroit / Piquette Street (Box 7)
  - Detroit River Recreation (Box 7)
  - Ren Center Redevelopment (Box 7)
  - Detroit Riverfront (Box 8)
  - Detroit Rivertown (Box 8)
  - Rouge River (Box 8)
  - Detroit Signage (Box 8)
  - Detroit Street Furniture (Box 8)
  - Detroit Symphony Orchestra (Box 8)
  - Detroit, University of (Box 8)
  - Detroit Warehouse (Box 8)
  - Detroit Water & Sewer District (Box 8)
  - DWSD-Central Yard (Box 8)
  - Detroit Woodward Ave. Plaza & Transit (Box 8)
  - Detroit Woodward Corridor (Box 8)
  - Detroit Woodward Mall (Box 8)
  - Detroit Zoo (Box 9)
  - Detroit Zoo Miscellanea (Box 9)
  - Delta College (Box 9)
  - Dexter (Box 9)
  - Domino's Farms (Box 9)
  - Domino's Farms Ave Maria (Box 9)
  - Domino's Farms Farmstead (Box 9)
  - Domino's The Settlement (Box 9)
  - Dow Office (Box 9)
  - Doyle Housing-Flint (Box 9)
  - Drummond Island (Box 10)
  - Farmington Hills Tech Park (Box 10)
  - Ferris State University (Box 10)
  - Fish Hatchery Sites (Box 10)
  - Flint City Center Plaza (Box 10)
  - Flint Cultural Center (Box 10)
  - Flint EZ (Box 10)
  - Flint Ink (Box 10)
  - Flint River (Box 10)
  - Flint West Village (Box 10)
  - Focus:HOPE (Box 10)
  - Foote Hospital (Box 10)
  - Ford Aerospace (Box 10)
  - Ford Fairlane (Box 10)
  - Ford-Henry Ford II Residence (Box 10)
  - Ford Highland Park (Box 10)
  - Ford Hospital (Box 10)
  - Ford-Rouge (Box 10)
  - Ford Motor Company World Headquarters (Box 10)
  - Ford Yacht Club (Box 10)
  - Fort Michilimackinac (Box 10)
  - Franklin Village, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Frankel Property (Box 11)
  - Frankenmuth (Box 11)
  - Fuller/Geddes (Box 11)
  - Gallup Park (Box 11)
  - Guardian Industries (Box 11)
  - Geddes Lake Townhouses (Box 11)
  - Geddes Road (Box 11)
  - General Motors (Box 11)
  - General Motors Institute (Box 11)
  - GM Buick, 0125 Cadillac (Box 11)
  - GM Clark Street (Box 11)
  - GM Milford Proving Grounds (Box 11)
  - GM New Center One (Box 11)
  - GM New Center CCDP Master Plan (Box 11)
  - GM New Center Improvements (Box 12)
  - GM New Center Park (Box 12)
  - GM New Center Properties (Box 12)
  - GM Tech Center (Box 12)
  - GM Truck and Bus (Box 12)
  - Genesee County Zoo (Box 12)
  - Gerson Residence 1999 (Box 12)
  - Gibraltar (Box 12)
  - Gibraltar Planning (Box 12)
  - Glacier Hills (Box 12)
  - Glacier Way (Box 12)
  - Glen Arbor, MI (Box 12)
  - Governor's Club (Box 12)
  - Grand Haven Bank (Box 12)
  - Grand Haven Cultural Center (Box 12)
  - Grand Haven Mall (Box 12)
  - Grand Rapids Beltline (Box 12)
  - Grand Rapids South Beltline (Box 12)
  - Grand Rapids Community College (Box 12)
  - Grand Rapids Condominiums (Box 13)
  - Grand Rapids Gas Company (Box 13)
  - Grand Rapids New Tram (Box 13)
  - Grand Rapids Riverfront (Box 13)
  - Grand Traverse Mall (Box 13)
  - Grand Traverse Civic Center (Box 13)
  - Grand Valley State University
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Grand Rapids Center (Box 13)
    - Retainer (Box 13)
  - Great Lakes Memorial Park (Box 13)
  - Greenfield Village (Box 13)
  - Greenhills School, Ann Arbor (Box 13)
  - Green Road Study (Box 13)
  - Grindstone City (Box 13)
  - Grindstone CZM Plan (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile Court Case (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile Drain (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile Entrance Sign Study (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile High School (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile-Lasalle (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile Marina (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile / Airport / Industrial Park (Box 13)
  - Grosse Ile Retainer (Box 14)
  - Grosse Ile Toll Bridge (Box 14)
  - Grosse Ile Township Waterline EIA (Box 14)
  - Grosse Ile Waters Edge Golf Course (Box 14)
  - Grosse Ile Zoning Signs (Box 14)
  - Grosse Pointe (Box 14)
  - Grosse Pointe Cadieux School (Box 14)
  - Grosse Pointe Farms Pier Park / Presentation (Box 14)
  - Grosse Pointe Village (Box 14)
  - Grosse Pointe Mack Avenue Entry Signs (Box 14)
  - Grosse Pointe Urban Design (Box 14)
  - Guardian Industries (Box 14)
  - Hampton Inn (Box 14)
  - Harbor Springs (Box 14)
  - Harbor Springs Park (Box 14)
  - Harbor Springs Rec. Plan (Box 14)
  - Harper Hospital (Box 14)
  - Harper Grace Hospital (Box 14)
  - Hastings (Box 14)
  - Health Care and Retirement Corporation (HCR) -- Detroit Edison Vivienne Farm Site (Box 14)
  - Henry Ford Hospital (Box 14)
  - Herman Gardens (Box 14)
  - Highland Park (Box 15)
  - Hillsdale Courthouse (Box 15)
  - Hills of Lone Pine (Box 15)
  - Historic Preservation
    - General (Box 15)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 15)
    - Battle Creek (Box 15)
    - Cadillac (Box 15)
    - Calumet (Box 15)
    - Chelsea (Box 15)
    - Cranbrook (Box 15)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 15)
    - Grand Traverse County Courthouse (Box 15)
    - Lansing (Box 15)
    - Marshall (Box 15)
    - Manchester (Box 15)
    - Michigan Historic Park Plan (Box 15)
    - Monroe (Box 15)
    - Olivet, MI (Box 15)
    - Saginaw (Box 15)
    - St. Ignace (Box 15)
    - Ypsilanti (Box 15)
  - Holland (Box 15)
  - Holly Township (Box 15)
  - Hoover Mansion (Box 15)
  - Howell, MI (Box 15)
  - Howell I-96 (Box 15)
  - J.L. Hudson Residence (Box 15)
  - Huron Parkway (Box 15)
  - Huron River EIS (Box 15)
  - Huron Towers (Box 15)
  - Huron Valley Girl Scout Camp (Box 15)
  - Huron Township (Box 15)
  - Huron Plaza (Box 15)
  - I-96 Howell (Box 16)
  - I-696 (Box 16)
  - Independence Township (Box 16)
  - Ingham County School District (Box 16)
  - Inkster Golf Course (Box 16)
  - Interlochen (Box 16)
  - Island Estate Boat Club (Box 16)
  - Island Estate Condos (Box 16)
  - ITI (Box 16)
  - Jackson, County of (Box 16)
  - Jackson National Life (Box 16)
  - OSOB Jackson (Box 16)
  - John Gard-Ann Arbor (Box 16)
  - John Gard-East Lansing (Box 16)
  - John Gard-West Bloomfield (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Carl-Graphic Class 7/1992 (Box 16)
  - Jos. Campau (Box 16)
  - Kalamazoo College (Box 16)
  - Kalamazoo Mall (Box 16)
  - Kellogg Foundation Built Project (Box 16)
  - Kellogg Foundation Site Photos (Box 16)
  - Kellogg Workplace (Box 16)
  - Kent Co. Int. Airport, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Kerrytown (missing) (Box 17)
  - Kmart (Box 17)
  - KMS Fusion (Box 17)
  - Knollwood (Box 17)
  - Kojaian Residence (Box 17)
  - Kresge Foundation (Box 17)
  - Kresge Foundation HDQ (Box 17)
  - L'arbre Croche Harbor Springs (Box 17)
  - Lake Orion-Guest House (Box 17)
  - Lake Superior State College (Box 17)
  - Lake Superior State University (Box 17)
  - Lambrecht E. Lansing (Box 17)
  - Lambrecht Oxford Housing (Box 17)
  - B Lambrecht Plymouth Housing (Box 17)
  - Lansing Bicentennial Park (Box 17)
  - Lansing Cap Development (Box 17)
  - Lansing Mall (Box 17)
  - Lansing Marketing Study (Box 17)
  - Lansing Urban Renewal Project (Box 17)
  - Lapeer Horizon of Homes Supervision (Box 17)
  - Lapeer Industrial Research Park (Box 17)
  - Lapeer Prison (Box 17)
  - Leelanau Homestead (Box 18)
  - Liberty Center-Troy (Box 18)
  - Liggett University Schools (Box 18)
  - Livingston Co. (Box 18)
  - Loch Alpine (Box 18)
  - M-37 Environmental Assessment (Box 18)
  - Maccabees Mutual Life (Box 18)
  - Macomb County Community College (Box 18)
  - Macomb County Community College Retainer (Box 18)
  - Mackinac Bridge Museum (Box 18)
  - Marshall, MI Brochure (Box 18)
  - Marquette University (Box 18)
  - Marquette Lakeshore Park Place (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens Bridgewater Twp (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens-Dixboro (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens Model (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens Pool (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens Rendering (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens Residence (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens Site (Box 18)
  - Matthaei Botanical Gardens South Main (Box 18)
  - Mazda (Box 18)
  - McManus-Jackson (Box 19)
  - McManus-Traverse City (Box 19)
  - MDSI (Box 19)
  - MDSI / Applicon (Box 19)
  - Meijer Belleville (Box 19)
  - Meijer Westland (Box 19)
  - Menominee, MI (Box 19)
  - Metro World Centre (Box 19)
  - Metro South Industrial Park (Box 19)
  - Michigan Aerial (Box 19)
  - N. Michigan Avenue (Box 19)
  - Michigan Bell (Box 19)
  - MBT Site Selection (Box 19)
  - Michigan Bell NW Office Center II (Box 19)
  - MBT-Flint (Box 19)
  - Mich. Economic Development Corp. (Box 19)
  - Michigan Horse Center (Box 19)
  - Michigan Natural Environmental Survey (Box 19)
  - Michigan State Fairgrounds (Box 19)
  - Michigan State Highway (Box 19)
  - Michigan State Housing Development Authority (Box 19)
  - Michigan State Housing Development Authority Kalamazoo (Box 19)
  - Michigan State Housing Development Authority Monroe (Box 19)
  - Michilimackinac (Box 19)
  - Michigan National (Box 19)
  - Michigan Waterworks Commission (Box 19)
  - MICOA (Box 19)
  - Midland Bridge (Box 20)
  - Midland Cemetery (Box 20)
  - Midland Hospital (Box 20)
  - Midland Main Street (Box 20)
  - Midland (Box 20)
  - Midland Parks (Box 20)
  - Midland Rec. Plan (Box 20)
  - Midwest Steel (Box 20)
  - Mill Creek (Box 20)
  - Milliken's Residence (Box 20)
  - Mott CC (Box 20)
  - Mt. Clemens (Box 20)
  - Mt. Pleasant (Box 20)
  - Muskegon CC (Box 20)
  - NBD-Farmington Hills (Box 20)
  - NBD Site Master Plan (Box 20)
  - New Museum of African History (Box 20)
  - Northern Michigan University (Box 20)
  - Northern Michigan University Houses by JJR (Box 20)
  - Northville Estates (Box 21)
  - Northville Hills (Box 21)
  - Northville Hills Corp Center (Box 21)
  - Northville Hills PUD 1997/1998 Toll Brothers (Box 21)
  - Northville Mill Pond (Box 21)
  - NSF (Box 21)
  - Oakland CC (Box 21)
  - Oakland University (Box 21)
  - Oakland University Classroom Office Building I (Box 21)
  - Oakland University Dorms (Box 21)
  - Orchard Lake Commercial Corridor (Box 21)
  - Orchard Lake Village (Box 21)
  - Orion Twp. Community Development Plant (Box 21)
  - Parke-Davis (Box 21)
  - Parker Property-Dixboro Road (Box 21)
  - Pentagon Centre Livonia (Box 21)
  - Pictured Rocks NLS (Box 21)
  - Pierce Lake (Box 22)
  - The Pinnacle (Box 22)
  - Pioneer High School-Ann Arbor (Box 22)
  - Pittsfield Ann Arbor Drain (Box 22)
  - Plymouth Congregational Church (Box 22)
  - Plymouth Education Park (Box 22)
  - Plymouth Hilton Inn (Box 22)
  - Plymouth Kellogg Park (Box 22)
  - Plymouth Park North (Box 22)
  - Plymouth Schools (Box 22)
  - Pontiac, MI-General (Box 22)
  - Pontiac Civic Center Model (Box 22)
  - Pontiac Downtown (Box 22)
  - Pontiac Osteopathic Hospital (Box 22)
  - Prince Corporation (Box 22)
  - Providence Hospital Brighton (Box 22)
  - Providence Hospital Westbrooke (Box 22)
  - Prudential Town Center (Box 22)
  - Rochester Hills (Box 22)
  - Romeo Arm. Inter. (Box 22)
  - Romeo Ford (Box 22)
  - Romeo Tractor Plant (Box 22)
  - Romulus City Hall/Library (Box 22)
  - Ross Roy (Box 22)
  - RPO Inkster Wetland (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Bay Pipeline (Box 22)
  - Saginaw County (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Economic Forum (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Federal Office Building (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Morley Park (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Morley Plaza (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Nature Center (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Riverfront (Box 22)
  - Saginaw Riverfront Development (Box 23)
  - Saginaw River Port (Box 23)
  - Saginaw Township (Box 23)
  - Salem Elementary School (Box 23)
  - Salom Grand West Bloomfield (Box 23)
  - Sauk Trails (Box 23)
  - Sauk Trail Landfill End Use (Box 23)
  - Sauk Trail Hills (Box 23)
  - Singh Pheasant Ridge (Box 23)
  - Sisters of Mercy (Box 23)
  - Soo Locks (Box 23)
  - Sosnick/Bauervic (Box 23)
  - Southfield Civic Center (Box 23)
  - Southfield / 8 Mile (Box 23)
  - Square Lake Road Office Park (Box 23)
  - St. Clair Development (Box 23)
  - St. John Hospital (Box 23)
  - St. Ignace (Box 23)
  - St. Joseph Harbor (Box 23)
  - Stables, The (Box 23)
  - State of Michigan Museum (Box 23)
  - State Library (Box 23)
  - State Library Archives (Box 23)
  - State Street (Box 23)
  - State Street Promenade (Box 24)
  - Sterling Hts. Housing (Box 24)
  - Stroh Brewery (Box 24)
  - Stroh's River / "Parke Davis" (Box 24)
  - Sugarloaf Mountain Resort (Box 24)
  - TC TALUS-Boardman River Crossing (Box 24)
  - Taylor/Holland Basin Wetland (Box 24)
  - Taylor Human Services (Box 24)
  - Terra W. Bloomfield Condos (Box 24)
  - Timbercrest (Box 24)
  - Timberlee Hills (Box 24)
  - Timberlee Cherry Square (Box 24)
  - Traverse City, 4 folders (Box 24)
  - Trenton (Box 24)
  - Turtle Creek (Box 24)
  - Tustian (Box 24)
  - University Park Presentation (Box 25)
  - Upjohn 300 Building (Box 25)
  - Upjohn Fine Chemicals (Box 25)
  - Upjohn Scio Ridge (Box 25)
  - Upper Peninsula Welcome Center (Box 25)
  - US Gypsum (Box 25)
  - Veterans Administration
    - Battle Creek (Box 25)
    - Cemetery, 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Cemetery Fort Custer (Box 25)
    - Medical Center, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Medical Center Allen Park, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Medical Center Detroit (Box 25)
  - Vernor / Springwells (Box 26)
  - Victor Corp. Park-Livonia (Box 26)
  - VIC Parks at Stonewood (Box 26)
  - Wabeek Farms (Box 26)
  - Waldenwoods (Box 26)
  - Ward Evangelical Presbyterian Church (Box 26)
  - Warren Valley Golf Outing (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Community College (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Co. Fuller-Geddes (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Co. Mental Retardation Svc (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Co. Soils, Maps (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Drain Allen Creek (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Hills Estates (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Intermediate School / Highpoint (Box 26)
  - Washtenaw Manor Nursing Home (Box 26)
  - Waterford Oaks (Box 26)
  - Wayne County CC (Box 26)
  - Wayne County Crosswinds Wetlands (Box 26)
  - Wayne Co. Ecorse (Box 26)
  - Wayne Co. Mental Hospital (Box 26)
  - Wayne County Parks (Box 26)
  - Wayne Co. Presentation (Box 26)
  - West Bloomfield (Box 26)
  - West Bloomfield Housing (Box 26)
  - West Bloomfield Township (Box 26)
  - West Dearborn DDA (Box 26)
  - Western Michigan University (Box 27)
  - Western Michigan University / Michigan State Hospital (Box 27)
  - Whitehall, MI (Box 27)
  - Willow Run Airport (Box 27)
  - Wyandotte (Box 27)
  - Wyandotte BASF (Box 27)
  - Wyandotte Eureka Viaducts (Box 27)
  - Yankee Air Force Museum (Box 27)
  - YMCA Burt Lake (Box 27)
  - YMCA Milford (Box 27)
  - York Township (Box 27)
  - Ypsilanti (Box 27)
  - Ypsilanti CBD (Box 27)
  - Ypsilanti Parkridge Park & Recreation (Box 27)
  - Ypsilanti Washington Street Mall (Box 27)
  - Zeeland High School (Box 27)
  - Zeeland Planning (Box 27)
- University of Michigan Project files
  - East Campus
    - East Campus (Box 27)
    - East Campus Graphics (Box 27)
  - Medical Campus (Box 28)
    - Med Campus Old Main (Box 28)
    - Medical Center (Box 28)
    - Med Center Brochure (Box 28)
    - Med. Center Master Plan (Box 28)
    - Med Center Parking Study (Box 28)
    - Med. Hospital Presentation (Box 28)
    - Med School (Box 28)
    - Cancer / Geriatrics (Box 29)
    - Eye Center (Kellogg) (Box 29)
    - Medical Center Glen Deck (Box 29)
    - Hospital Satellite Facility (Box 29)
    - Inglis House (Box 29)
    - Oxford Housing (Box 29)
    - Substance Abuse (Box 29)
    - UMRH (Box 29)
    - UMRH-Phasing (Box 29)
    - UMRH-Site Detail (Box 29)
  - Dearborn Campus
    - Dearborn (Box 29)
    - Dearborn College of Arts (Box 29)
    - Dearborn Main Entrance (Box 29)
    - Dearborn Phase II
  - Central Campus
    - General (Box 30)
    - Aerials Central Campus (Box 30)
    - Angell Hall (Box 30)
    - Brochure (Box 30)
    - Business School (Box 30)
    - Campus Model 1983 (Box 30)
    - Chemistry Building (Box 30)
    - Diag & Walkway (Box 30)
    - Identification Maps (Box 30)
    - Ingalls Mall (Box 30)
    - Kellogg Building (Box 30)
    - Law Quad (Box 30)
    - League Drop Off (Box 30)
    - Libraries (Box 30)
    - M. Bell Pool Addition (Box 30)
    - Modern Languages Building (Box 30)
    - Nickels Arcade (Box 31)
    - Physics and Astronomy (Box 31)
    - Palmer Field (Box 31)
    - E. Pedestrian Mall (Box 31)
    - Power Center (Box 31)
    - President's Residence (Box 31)
    - Randall Scheme Plan (Box 31)
    - Regents Plaza (Box 31)
    - State St Tunnel (Box 31)
    - Tappan Hall Addition (Box 31)
  - Flint Campus
    - Flint (Box 31)
    - Flint Autoworld (Box 31)
    - Court Street (Box 31)
    - Green Street (Box 31)
    - Graphics (Box 31)
    - Flint IMA Study / Ross House (Box 31)
    - Image Study 95 (Box 31)
    - Lighting (Box 31)
    - Flint-Numbered Duplicate (Box 31)